i'm just tapping in before i go eat my food and go to bed i don't speak spanish but you said
something about lips and so i'm blocking you because there is nothing about lips that you
should be saying to me even if i'm putting lipstick on labios no i don't like it um
okay y'all want to hear something i'm working on y'all want to hear something i'm working on
what i remember in one of the live we spoke about having an abortion i've never had an abortion
get out of my life and even if i had had an abortion why the fuck are you bringing that up
right now what if that was like a very traumatic experience for me can you get clarity on the mj love
what are you confused about a black man who had the world in the palm of his hand
was accused of being a pedophile an entire cabal of individuals
have been more than just abused accused but have been truly proven to be
and ain't shit happening i mean literally just i i feel like it just
val said moderate me please moderate me exactly influential 525 underscore 44 like the math is
so basic like it's not algebra it's not algebra michael jackson exactly la spring michael jackson
owned the beatles catalog like what are we talking about y'all need to be able to put things together
anything that mainstream media tells you is a goddamn lie and i just wish you all would
fucking put that together because it's really not something that just started
okay so i don't got a single question and michael michael jackson forever
okay michael jackson forever do y'all want to hear this song that i'm working on yes okay
all you had to go is pay us enough to shove them from other sick executives
a ruling class that laughs in caste system ha ha ha ha ha i need to deck them in the halls
they never see the people coming even when they from us
never feel the power humming because it's from within us
indigenous all talk on us
rule by the moon before the dollar with the idol
before there was a bible
before we were all trained and walking
we'll file and pledge allegiance to politicians
communal vision
i hope you're listening i hope you're listening
because buddy with that lighter at the end of his rope
will do more than murder
because the supply chain choked
that warehouse was a burial ground of desires
you just flew free as the flames grew
higher
you just flew free as the green blue
because it's got us in a chokehold
or conundrum if you will
if we move we are a target
but get killed sitting still
sitting bull
with a full clip
for the people
we ain't going nowhere
standing rock solid seal
is what the people do
they've done it for millennia
palestini
and algon
when we're hot
and maori
galakichi
sanosa
we longer to defeat
keep the world in fear
to forget the joy of peace
all this on my mind
how do i sleep
with one eye open
ready to receive
and first of all
thank you for all of the dope responses
someone in the comment said
you've got a lot of free time on your hands
this is not free time
this this is my job
hello
big up grenada
this is my job
this is my whole purpose
so
june 14th
and um
i have no idea
why people feel
like they should give me
critique
i just i don't know
i just blocked somebody
who said
i don't love the snare
go fuck yourself
i love the snare
i don't love the snare
who are you
please gain some courage
please y'all
please
who's they
that's mad at me
about the met
who's they
nobody i respect
is mad at me
about the met
believe that
not a single person
i respect
you know what i also
want y'all to know
like
sometimes you be feeling
like damn
like these people
don't fuck with me
and then if you
really think about it
you're like
but i don't like them
like them
and then you keep going
talking about
you should add
some ghost notes
shut up
ghost notes
the shirt
i forgot
somebody gave this to me
anyways
how can you not
like the snare
that's it
that's the hip hop
of it all
a kick and a snare
guitar licks
like live instruments
so
you know
people are asking
like
you know
people are asking
for like more sounds
the point of the beat
is it has space
right
so sometimes
you want it to be
like super full
and like really
like
a lot
you know
like alive
in a different way
and this
i'm saying so much
in the lyrics
of this song
that i want it
to have space
i want it to have
like air
okay
and so
you also have to remember
like where i come from
i'm from the 90s
like i am
a 90s hip hop head
and so
there's
a certain aesthetic
that i'm going for
when i'm trying to bring
certain things across
and
you know like
you know on this record
it started with just
the drums
and the bass
and then i built it up
and then i realized
oh
because as i've been
putting together this album
it's my beat
as i've been putting
together this album
all i've been listening to
is like
bob marley
and peter tosh
and jimmy cliff
however
you know
once you're
once you're in producer mode
it's okay
so when i was a comic
when i was doing stand-up
i mean i'm always a comic
for life
but when i would be
in stand-up mode
like my brain would shift
because
when you're in joke writing mode
like you have to have
such a super awareness
at all fucking time
and a hyper awareness
like i don't know
some people can exist
in that all the time
i don't
but
that's what i would do
so like
in producer mode
right now
when i'm listening to music
i'm not vibing
i'm listening
and breaking down
every single sound
and like when i was
in elementary school
our music class
we used to play music bingo
and
we would literally
have to
we would
we would know
whether our
square
has like a certain
whether we would
get a certain square
on if we could
hear the instrument
so like i was taught
very very early on
to be able to
pick out instruments
from like
a whole orchestra
so if you play a beat
for me i can tell you
like every single sound
in the beat
you know how some people
can do that with wine
like oh there's like
tannins
and and and hints
of smoke
so
when i'm listening
to records
so when i was
in the car today
listening to
um off the wall
no i was listening
to the thriller today
um
actually did i listen
to don't stop
to get enough today
i think it was
they had like a
they had a
a high hat
that started
no
i was listening
to fleetwood mac
today
and
in
um
do
break the chain
they have a high hat
that starts
low
and then it
crescendos
you know what
crescendo means
it gets louder
right so they have
this high hat
that starts low
and i was like
oh i gotta put
that in here
you hear it
it's coming
try to
kind of bring
an analog
to the digital
so like
sometimes
some people
want their track
to be like
perfectly
like aligned
on the grid
for the mix
i told my engineer
like my nigga
you gonna have to
thug it the fuck out
because i'm gonna
play the high hats
by hand
and i'll
you know
i'll go after
and line them up
a little bit
better
but i'll play it
by hand
you know
like it took me
for fucking
ever
to figure out
these chords
um
so anyways
my album is
coming out
on june 14th
i will be doing
a series
of listening
sessions
across the
that's right
trayshaun
across the
nation
we're about to
put it together
but for those
who are in
new york
you can mark
your calendar
for june 17th
um
and uh
yeah
so
thank y'all
for listening
and
uh
you know
just
sometimes
you know
i'm in here
by myself
you know
i'm saying
so
sometimes
i just
want to
like
engage
with some
folks
because a
lot of
times
you know
the studio
beast
is supposed
the studio
is a lot
of times
a whole
community
affair
but sometimes
i just
be in here
but you
know
i'm in here
by myself
so
y'all be
my community
affair
sometimes
so thank
y'all for
listening
and um
someone in
here said
how come
every skill
you do
is such
high quality
and i
really want
to appreciate
i really
want to tell
you i
appreciate
that and
the reason
is
because i
treat
everything
as a
craft
not as
commerce
that's why
because
we have
been trained
particularly in
the united
states but
just in western
culture to
treat everything
as how do i
make money
off of this
and that
ends up
making people
rush
that ends
up making
people
shortcut
that ends
up making
people steal
and i
don't look
at it like
that i
look at
it as
a craft
and an
art form
which is
something that
you should
honor right
because it's
a gift
it's it's
something being
like brought
to you
and if
you think
trees are
majestic
like trees
bear right
so they
bear blooms
they bear
fruit they
bear leaves
right they
bear they
bear seeds
we as
humans we
bear you
know we
may bear
humans but
if you're a
creative like
that's part of
what you bear
i'm a creative
baron tree
so i don't
just want
anything so
um look
for the live
where lindsey
is singing to
stevie i have
no idea what
that context
is so
anyways i hope
you all enjoy
i hope y'all
have a great
evening and
uh i hope
that you are
i hope you
enjoy the
work the
music when
it comes
out